otavo.tv 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Watch Online Episodes Full Movies | Otavo TV

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number information.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**To personalize your experience**

(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)

**To improve our website**

(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)

**To improve customer service**

(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)

**To process transactions**

(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

**To send periodic emails**

( The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Otavo TV contains links to other websites. We do not exercise control over their policies regarding the confidentiality of your personal information. Your use of websites to which we link is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on such third party websites.

**Security**

Otavo TV is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We have put in place suitable procedural and technological measures meant to protect your data from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

**Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, with or without notice. However, we will inform you if there are changes which can actually affect your rights. We encourage users to be responsible regarding the confidentiality of their personal information and to check every now and then the rules stipulated by this privacy policy in order to update their preferences.

If you have any questions or suggestions, feel free to address them through our **[Contact Form](http://otavo.tv/contact)**.
